{
    "subject": "resource/Arthur_Wilkinson",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:British_composers",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Wilkinson is a subject of Category:British_composers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8319244384765625,
            "question": "Is Arthur Wilkinson known for composing music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8039857745170593,
            "question": "To what category does Arthur Wilkinson belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7354429960250854,
            "question": "What era did Arthur Wilkinson compose in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5532670021057129,
            "question": "What nationality is Arthur Wilkinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5431022644042969,
            "question": "What is known about Arthur Wilkinson's life outside of composing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48526567220687866,
            "question": "Were there any notable musical influences on Arthur Wilkinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41486096382141113,
            "question": "Did Arthur Wilkinson receive any awards for his compositions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40817996859550476,
            "question": "What instruments did Arthur Wilkinson's music often feature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3833795487880707,
            "question": "Where was Arthur Wilkinson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3402436673641205,
            "question": "Can you name any famous works by Arthur Wilkinson?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Wilkinson is a subject of Category:British_composers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1073_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Arthur Wilkinson born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1073_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments did Arthur Wilkinson's music often feature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1073_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Arthur Wilkinson receive any awards for his compositions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1073_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1073_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide information about Arthur Wilkinson, including his occupation as a composer and his work on various musical projects. This suggests that he can be classified under the category \"Category:British_composers\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Arthur Wilkinson, including his profession as a composer. Given that he was a British composer, the triple \"Arthur Wilkinson is a subject of Category:British_composers\" can be considered correct based on the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}